Guide to the Charles Baptie photograph collection, 1917-1995
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 17: Vehicles, 1946-1995
  - Vehicles/Transportation, 1930s, 1950s, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 17)
    Photographs of various forms of transportation.
  - Vehicles, 1940s-1950s (Box 25)
    Photographs of a B-20.
  - Vehicles, 1970s (Box 26)
  - Vehicles, 1957 (Box 27)
    Images of a vehicle.
  - Vehicles, 1950s, 1970s (Box 30)
    Images of vehicles.
  - Vehicles, 1940s-1950s (Box 33)
    Photographs of vehicles, including those of the Air Force.
  - Vehicles, 1970s (Box 36)
    Pictures of boxcars.
  - Vehicles, 1980s (Box 37)
    Pictures of a space shuttle, aircraft, and hot air balloons.
  - Vehicles, 1993 (Box 38)
    Pictures of a boat and car and the Gunston Hall car show
  - Vehicles, 1949 (Box 41)
    Picture of President Truman on an Air Transport Command plane.
  - Vehicles, undated (Box 43)
    Photographs of a plane, as well as Air Traffic Command.
  - Vehicles, 1951 (Box 45)
    Picture of a dual drive Army Jeep.
  - Vehicles, 1953 (Box 47)
    Images of Thompson trailers and Gunston Hall cars.
  - Vehicles, 1970s (Box 52)
    Photographs of a special locomotive ceremony.
  - Vehicles, 1957 (Box 56)
    Images of Pan 1957 vehicles.
  - I Watched Eisenhower Campaign, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Vehicles, 1940s-1950s (Box 62)
    Pictures of airplanes and a car fire.
  - Vehicles and animals, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Photograph of a truck on fire on a small highway and a car in a showroom.
  - Vehicles, 1950s, 1970s (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous pictures and negatives, 1950s (Box 69, Folder 7)
    Images of planes.
- Series 18: Gunston Hall, 1960s-1993
  This series contains photographs and negatives of Gunston Hall, home of George Mason. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary. Images include the Mason coat of arms, publications, postcard images, aerial views, and a car show.
  - , 1960s, 1970s, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1-19)
    Images of Gunston Hall, as well as the Mason Coat of Arms, publications, the Prophetic Pineapple of Gunston Hall, and postcard. (with negatives and slides)
  - Gunston Hall pamphlet, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Gunston Hall, undated (Box 27)
    Photographs of Gunston Hall.
  - Gunston Hall, 1990 (Box 36)
  - Gunston Hall, 1990, 1993 (Box 38)
    Aerial shots of Gunston Hall. Also, images of a car show held at Gunston Hall.
  - Gunston Hall, 1975 (Box 62)
    Images of Gunston Hall, including publication negatives and large format prints.
  - Gunston Hall, 1970s (Box 65)
- Series 19: International, 1958-1989
  This series contains photographs and negatives of various settings in Central America, like Brazil, Honduras, and Ecuador; and other international locations, like Paris or India. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary.
  - Papers for Brazil publication, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Papers for a publication about Brazil.
  - Malaria prevention, 1960s (Box 29)
    Images of malaria prevention and testing in Honduras and Ecuador.
  - Malaria prevention, 1960s (Box 31)
  - France, 1980s (Box 35)
    Pictures of Paris.
  - Malaria prevention, 1960s (Box 39)
  - Malaria prevention, 1960s (Box 40)
  - Taj Mahal, 1970s (Box 47)
    Photograph of the Taj Mahal.
  - Malaria prevention, 1960s (Box 48)
  - Malaria prevention, 1960s (Box 50)
  - Eiffel Tower and Buildings, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Picture of the Eiffel Tower during its 100th anniversary.
- Series 20: Correspondence, 1955-1990s
  This series contains correspondence between Charles Baptie and others about photograph orders and publications.
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972-1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Letters written to and from Charles Baptie.
  - Papers, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Letters written to and from Charles Baptie regarding publication information.
  - Papers, 1990s and earlier (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Series 21: Electric Media, 1970s-1980s
  This series contains electronic media, specifically a couple of floppy disks for a computer program called Wordstar.
  - Electronic Media, 1970s-1980s (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Out-dated 5 1/4 inch computer floppy discs.